快来 麦克斯 课程要开始啦
Come on, Max! Class is starting.
我给你预留了我旁边的位置
I saved you a spot next to me.
马上来 等我先把巨乳绑好
Be right there. Strapping in the girls.
左咪今天有点暴躁
Lefty's a little cranky this morning.
感谢你把这些健身带
Thanks for getting these work out bands
从健身房的垃圾堆里捡回来
out of the Equinox dumpster.
我当时人都在里面了嘛
I was already in there.
我跟我的会计约在那里见面
I had a meeting with my accountant.
对了 我们生意不太好啊
We're not doing great, by the way.
我们可以用这些健身带做阻力训练
We're gonna do resistance work with them.
我已经够有阻力了
I'm already resistant.
我简直都要是暴力了好吗
I'm almost at violent.
跟我做
Do what I'm doing.
露出股沟吗
Let my crack stick out?
屁股动起来 摆动 再摆动
And pulse, and pulse, and pulse.
我来帮你把脉搏[摆动]停下吧
Let me just get rid of that pulse for you.
别闹了 麦克斯上次药店的机器说
Come on, Max, the heart machine at Rite Aid said you were 80
你的心脏等同80岁老人 还让你去买轮椅
and printed you a prescription for a wheelchair.
数到三开始
On the count of three.
一 二 三
One, two, three.
有床压在我身上吗
Is there a bed on me?
把我的轮椅推来
Get my wheelchair.
姑娘们
Hey, girls.
快看芭芭拉的新车
Check out Barbara's new ride.
我们需要帮助
We need help.
而且不单是因为芭芭拉比我先拥有豪华SUV
And not just because Barbara has a luxury SUV before I do.
很棒的健身
Great workout.
我要吃个贝果放松一下
I'm gonna cool down with a bagel.
我下楼只是为了给你送信
No, I just came down here to bring you your mail.
而芭芭拉想来炫耀她的新车
And Barbara wanted to show off her car
给你们俩穷光蛋看
because you girls are poor.
迟交的手机账单 电费...
Overdue cell phone bill, electricity--
苏菲 这些信都是上个月的了
Sophie, this mail is from a month ago.
怎么 信又不怕放 又不像茅屋起司
What? It's mail, not cottage cheese.
等等 里面好像是有一点茅屋起司
Oh, wait. I think there might be a little cottage cheese in there.
还有起司能让我沾着贝果吃吗
Got any of that for my bagel?
天啊
Oh, my God.
我的人生大电影要上映了
The movie they're making about my life is coming out.
名字是叫"天赐无聊"吗
Is it called Good Will Boring?
麦克斯 我们被邀请去参加媒体餐会
And Max, we're invited to the press junket
来宣传电影
to promote the movie.
两天后
In two days?
我觉得连我的那位发型师都来不及救你
I don't even think my hair girl could help you in time
而且她有三只手呢
and she's got three hands.
苏菲 希望我们还来得及表示出席
Sophie, I hope it's not too late to RSVP.
我一直在等有关这部电影的消息
I was waiting for some news about the movie.
差点以为所托非人呢
I thought it went to the wrong person.
就像我20多岁的人生
Like my 20s.
走吧 芭芭拉 咱们去游乐场绕街
Come on, Barbara. Let's cruise the playground
嘲笑开电动车的其他宝宝
and make fun of babies in Chevy Volts.
芭芭拉能顺路放我在健身房下车吗
Uh, can Barbara drop me off at Equinox?
他们会在3点30丢掉过期的能量棒
They throw out the expired Clif Bars at 3:30.
阿憨 麦克斯跟我得出席我电影的记者会
Oh, Han, Max and I have to do press for my movie,
所以明天没法上班
so we can't work tomorrow.
能理解 哪能打破您6年的旷工记录呢
I get it. Why break your six-year streak?
等你拿到了你电影的钱
I guess with all your movie money,
你们能幸福高飞 我也能请两位新的
you two can move on and I can hire two waitresses
不会把我办公室当赌场的服务员
who don't use my office as a gambling hall.
阿憨 卡洛琳已经把从电影赚来的钱
Han, Caroline already spent all the movie money
全投进甜品酒吧了
on the dessert bar.
另外 20分钟后我要用你的办公室
Also, I need your office in 20 minutes.
我们要面试新的轮盘赌荷官
We're interviewing a new roulette dealer.
那你能好歹告诉他们
Well, can you at least tell people
别用我的家庭相片熄烟吗
not to put cigarettes out on my family photos?
我奶奶都被烧一个大洞了
There's a giant hole in my grandma.
他们把演员名单发来了
Ooh! They just sent a cast list.
猜猜是谁扮演我
Guess who's playing me?
苔丝·沃克
Tess Walker.
她是个很大...
She is a very big--
等等 我读一下她大在哪里
hold on, let me read what she's a very big.
如果是胸部 那他们真是完全没调查过你
If it's big-boobed, they did zero research.
她来自澳大利亚 是个冉冉上升的新星
Tess is from Australia. She's a rising star
出道作品为浪漫喜剧"泥嚎凯特"
and got her start in the romantic comedy G'day Kate.
麦克斯 你的角色将由瓦妮莎·罗宾森
Max, you're being played by Vanessa Robinson.
一个小咖 不是女主都这样
Not a name, but that's what they do.
瓦妮莎·罗宾森吗
Vanessa Robinson?
她主持我最爱的迪士尼节目
She's on my favorite Disney show,
"真是太瓦妮莎·罗宾森啦"
That's So Vanessa Robinson.
他们怎么会指望迪士尼傻白甜来演我啊
How do they expect a Disney goody-two-shoes to play me?
她演不出真的吸嗨 喝醉
She won't be realistic playing high or drunk
或是跟电影《荒野猎人》里熊搏斗的样子
or fighting the bear from The Revenant.
麦克斯 谁演我啊
Ooh, Max, who's playing me?
米雪儿·金
Michelle Kim?
是女人来演我吗
I'm being played by a woman?
冷静 不是女人 是个11岁女孩
Calm down, not a woman. It's an 11-year-old girl.
而且人家估计比你还不爽好吗
And she's probably more upset about it than you are.
真是天方夜谭
That's preposterous.
11岁小女孩怎么可能是餐厅老板
An 11-year-old girl couldn't own a diner.
你就是啊
You do.
两位 我把你们的午餐拿来啦
Hey, guys. I picked up your lunch.
还有另外两份从这里点的外卖
There were two other orders from customers in here.
鲍比 苔丝·沃克要在电影里扮演我
Bobby, Tess Walker is playing me in the movie about me.
"泥嚎凯特"的那个啊
From G'day Kate!
她是凯特对吧
Oh, yeah. She's Kate, right?
还是里面对凯特说"泥嚎"的那个人
Or or the one that says "G'day" to her?
无论是哪个 都没你漂亮
Either way, she's not as pretty as you.
你总是知道该说哪句我教你的话
Ohh, you know exactly what I tell you to say.
不是我们店里做的薯条好好吃啊
Ooh, the fries are good from not here.
奥列格 过来尝尝
Oleg, try these.
奥列格
Hey, Oleg.
上面写皮特·奇尔顿来扮演你
It says here you're being played by Pete Chilton.
天啊 他就是我们一起看过的搞笑电影里
My gosh, he's the one who played the serial killer
扮演连环杀手的那个人
in that funny movie we saw.
希望他下面大小与我一致
I hope the penis is accurate.
他会正面全裸对吧
This is a full frontal role, right?
反正咱们店里是这样
It is here.
上面貌似没有苏菲这个角色
Oh, it doesn't look like there's a Sophie character.
但有个角色叫珍珠
Oh, but there is one named Pearl,
是餐厅收银员 她是一名黑人波兰妞
a Black Polish woman who works as the diner's cashier.
什么
What?
他们居然把我跟厄尔合一了
They combined me with Earl?
如果我想要跟任何人合一
I mean, if I wanted to be combined with someone,
我就不会宁愿放弃一个肾
I wouldn't have given up a liver
也要跟我的连体姐妹分开了
to be separated from my twin.
他们把我变成了女人吗
Hey, they made me a woman?
我上一次假扮女人 还是想跟玛丽莲·梦露
I haven't been a woman since I was trying to outrun
逃出黑帮魔爪的时候
the mob with Marilyn Monroe.
天啊 卡洛琳
Oh, holy crap, Caroline.
这部电影里有你前男友糖果安迪这角色
Your ex Candy Andy's a character in the movie
他本人也会出现在媒体毒会
and he's gonna be at the press junkie.
是餐会 你才是毒会[虫] 别搞混了
Junket. You're a junkie, get it right.
还有糖果安迪 他为什么会出现在电影里
And Candy Andy? Why is he in the movie?
这个年纪应该可以叫唐国·安德鲁了吧
Shouldn't he be old enough to go by Candrew Andrew at this point?
鲍比 在你疯狂吃干醋之前
Bobby, before you get crazy jealous,
我想说他帅到翻
he is very handsome
而且我跟他在床事上
and I went places with him sexually
到达过我个人从未到过之境
that I had never been before.
但无论如何 我现在跟你在一起 他也结婚了
But--ah, anyway, I'm with you, now, and he's married.
很棒啊 我... 真的不是会吃醋的那种男人
That's cool, I'm just-- I'm just not a jealous guy.
我对我们岩石般稳固的爱情有信心
I am confident in our rock solid relationship.
这样就很讨人厌了
Well, that's very annoying.
这么多的记者跟摄影师让我想起
All these reporters and photographers remind me
当年我掉乳牙时的场景
of when I lost my baby teeth.
我爸在我枕头底下留了一间避暑别墅
Oh, my father left a summer home under my pillow.
我乳牙是终极格斗赛上被明星女格斗家打掉的
I left my baby teeth in the octagon with Ronda Rousey.
这是个给我们甜品酒吧做广告的好机会
This would be a great opportunity to plug our dessert bar.
咱们先绕一圈然后小声谈论我们的店
Let's do a lap and start whispering about ourselves
来引起大家兴趣
to get a buzz going.
如果你觉得都早上11点了我还没嗨[兴趣]上
If you think I don't already have a buzz going at 11:00 A.M.,
那你真是太不了解我了
then you don't know me.
天啊 那是苏菲跟厄尔的合体
Oh, my God, that's the Sophie and Earl mash-up.
她是迪士尼《女孩看世界》的美式足球教练
She was the football coach on Girl Meets World!
越来越像回事啦
This is getting real!
卡洛琳·钱宁吗
Caroline Channing?
我叫黛西 我是公关团队的人
I'm Daisy. I'm with the PR team.
你有可能听说过我 卡戴珊同父异母的妹妹
Maybe you've heard of me. Kylie Jenner threw
去年往我头上扔了整瓶雪碧
a full can of Sprite at my head last year.
这就是为什么我的瞳孔这么大
That's why my pupils are so big!
黛西 别担心 我这人不难搞
Daisy, don't worry. I am not high maintenance.
我怎么样才能确保我所有的照片
How can I be sure that all photos of me
全都拍我的右侧脸呢
are taken on the north side of my face?
我叫麦克斯
I'm Max.
当你的瞳孔消失时 是代表什么意思
Uh, what does it mean when you don't have pupils?
你们真是太萌了
You guys are so cute.
我知道你们还没看过这部电影
Oh, I know you haven't seen the movie,
所以我简单告诉你们一下剧情
so I'll give you a quick rundown of what happens
好应付媒体提问
for press questions.
我看看 你损失所有财产
Uh, let's see. You lose your money.
惨惨惨 然后你遇到她
Sad, sad, sad. And then you meet this one.
惨惨惨
Sad, sad, sad.
你真是太萌了
You are so cute.
电影已经不单纯只是说你们两个了
It's not as much about the two of you anymore.
故事情节有点拉拉味儿
The storyline came off a little lesbionic,
坦白说 挺去年的炒作法
which is kinda last year.
我也有点拉拉味儿
I just came off a little lesbionic.
有小妞一直不停打电话找我
Maggie won't stop calling me.
天啊
Oh, my God.
苔丝来了 她真是完美无瑕
There's Tess. Oh, she's flawless.
饰演我的完美人选
She's the perfect me.
苔丝 是我 你 卡洛琳
Tess, It's me! You, Caroline!
扮演你的姑娘还没到场
Oh, and the young lady playing you hasn't shown up yet.
真的麦克斯本人也应该缺席
Oh, that's what the real Max should've done.
你真是太萌了 她下了狠心研究
You're so cute. No, she went real method
就为了进入你这角色的状态
in researching the role of you.
她现在对毒品严重上瘾了
And now she's real into drugs.
我超难过 但是你们看不出
I'm so upset. You just can't tell
因为我吃很强的抗忧郁药
because I'm heavily medicated.
你好啊 没人看管的酒吧
Hello, unattended bar.
卡洛琳·钱宁本人
Caroline Channing in person.
这感觉想必与当年
Oh, this must be what it was like
茱莉娅·罗伯茨与艾琳·布劳克维奇相遇一样
when Julia Roberts met Erin Brockovich.
或者反过来 我是罗伯茨
Or the other way around.
他是布伦特 饰演糖果安迪
Oh, and this is Brent, the actor playing Candy Andy.
我们两个之间应该尴尬一下
Should it be awkward between us
因为你饰演我多年来唯二的
since you're playing one in a long string
前男友之一吗
of two ex-boyfriends?
谢谢
Thanks.
谢谢您如此悲催的人生
Thanks for having a tragic life
我才有机会在戏里坠入爱河
so I could fall in love on screen.
戏外亦然
And off.
我觉得观众们会比较想看到我
Uh, see, I think audiences would much rather see me
跟一个... 比如说劳动阶级的
wind up with, let's say, a working class,
可能名字叫鲍比的蓝领包工头在一起
blue collar contractor, maybe named Bobby.
你真萌 但是不行 因为很明显
You're so cute. No, it was pretty obvious
大家都觉得你应该跟糖果安迪在一起
to everyone you should wind up with Candy Andy.
我也这么觉得
Yeah, I thought so, too.
糖果安迪
Candy Andy!
我现在不用这个傻名字了 麦克斯
I do not go by that silly name, Max.
我现在叫唐国·安德鲁
It's Candrew Andrew.
安德鲁
Andrew.
你看起来很不错
You look great.
对不起
Oh, sorry, ooh.
你们两个看起来就像我跟我八年级的科学老师
You two are like me and my eighth grade science teacher.
总是忍不住对对方上下其手
Just can't keep your hands off each other.
麦克斯 你毁了你老师的一生
Max, you ruined Mr. Brillstein's life,
而安迪也像你老师一样 是有妇之夫
and, like Mr. Brillstein, Andy is married.
其实我离婚了
Oh, uh, well, actually I'm divorced.
这就是你奈特·沙马兰级的剧情翻转
There's your M. Night Shyamalan twist!
但电影其他部分还是别让他导了
But don't let him direct the rest of the movie.
让摄影师给两位拍个照可以吗
Oh, how about a picture of you two for the photographers?
你们看起来很般配
You look great together.
你的婚姻走到尽头我深感遗憾
I'm sorry your marriage didn't work out.
我也是
Yeah, me too.
我岳父有纽约流浪者队的贵宾席票呢
My father-in-law had box seats to the Rangers.
你看起来真美
You look beautiful.
你嘴唇上有我的口红
You have my lipstick on your mouth.
有可能只是我们刚好擦了同款
Oh, well, maybe we wear the same shade.
这杯6... 27块
That'll be six--ehh, $27.
厄尔 不用起了
Hey, Earl. Don't get up.
想起也起不来 除非有公司
No chance of that, unless they start
开始制造给整个身体用的伟哥
making Viagra for the entire body.
卡洛琳不在 你来干嘛
Uh, Caroline's not here. What do you need?
其实我来是想找你们聊聊
Actually, I wanted to talk to you guys.
虽然她曾告诫我千万不要这么做
Even though she told me never to do that.
你们想看长得像原始摩登人的咪咪头吗
You guys wanna see a nipple that looks like Fred Flintstone?
现在我知道原因了
Now I see why.
如果是想推销安利 我已经受骗上当过两次了
If this is an Amway pitch, I've fallen for that twice.
这么说吧 推销推我上债台下地狱
Let's just say I am way in debt.
不是啦 是关于那个叫安迪的家伙
No, it's this--this Andy guy.
你们能跟我说说他的情况吗
What can you tell me about him?
他帅吗 有钱吗
Is he good looking? Rich?
他是亚马逊的金牌会员吗 我要愁死了
Does he have Amazon Prime? I'm dying, here.
我还以为你不是爱吃醋的那种人
Oh, I thought you weren't the jealous type.
可你就像瘦版的乔纳·希尔试图搞笑
But you're sweating like skinny Jonah Hill trying to be funny
或肥版的乔纳·希尔试图正经时那样喷汗
or fat Jonah Hill trying to be serious.
我就是爱吃醋的那种人
Well, I am the jealous type.
我只是想在卡洛琳面前扮酷而已
I just wanted to look cool in front of Caroline.
我才不在乎在你们面前形象如何
I don't care what I look like in front of you guys.
明显看得出
Obviously.
你没什么可担心的 安迪
You have nothing to worry about, Andy.
我是说 鲍比
I mean, Bobby.
这情况非常像
Much like the copy of TV Guide
厄尔正在读的《电视指南》旧刊
Earl is currently reading,
糖果安迪早是旧闻了
Candy Andy is old news.
你们知道今晚要播最新一集的《生命的事实》吗
Ooh, there's another episode of Facts of Life tonight, you know?
大家安...
Hey, everybo--
难道你不想帮我把句子说完吗 厄尔
Wouldn't you like to finish that sentence for me, Earl?
反正你在卡洛琳的电影里也没有属于自己的角色
Since you don't have your own character in Caroline's movie.
没错 你们说得对
Yeah, you're right.
我没什么好担心的
I got nothing to worry about.
我该走了
I should get going.
安迪
Hey, Andy.
我是叫 鲍比
I mean, Bobby.
快看 你有看见这张
Look, did you see this picture
卡洛琳和糖果安迪的合影吗
of Caroline with Candy Andy?
瞧瞧 他在餐会上用胳膊搂着她
Look, he's got his arm around her at a junket.
他的手是放在她的背部下方还是屁股上方
Is that hand on her lower back or upper butt?
兄弟 还好你不是爱吃醋的那种人
Hey, man, it's a good thing you're not the jealous type.
尤其是因为他把手放在她屁股那儿
Especially since he has his hand right on her ass.
喂 我才刚想说这句话
Hey...I was gonna say that!
你就不能别什么东西都跟我抢吗 厄尔
Can you at least give me one thing of my own, Earl?
我去我们的卡座了
I'll be in our booth.
我代表《纽约时报》
I'm from the New York Times.
你怎么会沦落到这种地方
Ha, what the hell are you doing here?
我有个问题问苔丝
I have a question for Tess.
在"泥嚎凯特"里 你为了绿卡跟一只袋鼠结婚是吗
In G'day Kate, you married a kangaroo for a green card?
感觉真是超级怪 对吧
So this is super weird, right?
看着他们 扮演我们
Looking at them, being us.
安迪 我现在不能说话 我得推广我们酒吧
Andy, I can't talk now. I have to promote my dessert bar
还得回答所有媒体的问题
and answer all these questions.
你也知道当记者碰到
You know how reporters get
一个吸引人的话题时他们会怎么样
when they have a fascinating subject.
卡洛琳 没人问你问题
Caroline, no one's asked you anything
而且人家早就告诉你 不要再举手示意了
and they already told you to stop raising your hand.
麦克斯 饰演你的演员没来
Max, the actress playing you isn't here.
据报道自从她进入你这个角色后
It's been reported she's been on a downward spiral
生活堕落事业下滑
ever since she got into the role.
她的行为令人厌恶
Her behavior is disgusting,
而我表示非常赞同
and I very much approve.
有个问题想问米雪儿 饰演阿憨一角的小妹妹
This is for Michelle, the young lady playing the Han character.
你为什么想饰演这个角色
What drove you to the role?
我妈说如果我想无限流量上网
My mom said I had to start helping out in this family
那就得开始出来赚钱养家
if I wanted unlimited data.
饰演珍珠一角的珍妮儿
And for Janelle, portraying Pearl,
你是如何准备演绎一个集黑人
how did you prepare to play a Black man
和比常人大一号的波兰女人于一体的角色
and a larger-than-life Polish woman?
两个口音教练 外加大量假发
Two dialogue coaches and a lot of wigs.
我一接到奥列格这个角色后 就再也没有洗过澡了
And I stopped showering the minute I got the role of Oleg.
卡洛琳 我有个关于咱俩的问题想问你
Caroline, I have a question for you about us.
问答会不是让你提问的地方
A Q & A is not the place for questions.
好吧 那我不问了
Well, fine, I won't ask you, then.
我就直接说吧
I'll just tell you.
我想你 想你那可爱的歪嘴一笑
I miss you and your adorable crooked smile.
瞧瞧好莱坞版的我们
I mean, look at the Hollywood us.
我们可以成为现实生活中的他们
We could be the real version of them.
不过我可不会画眼线
Just, you know, I wouldn't wear guyliner.
卡洛琳 命运让我们相遇肯定是有原因的
Caroline, fate brought us together for a reason.
我们曾拥有美好的爱情
I mean, we had a really good thing.
我觉得我们应该再给彼此一个机会
I think we should give it another shot.
卡洛琳·钱宁 你刚说你现在经营一家甜品酒吧是吗
Caroline Channing, you said you own a dessert bar now?
卡洛琳居然说不出话来了
Caroline's speechless.
看来向神灯许的愿望只剩两个没实现
Guess I'm down to two wishes on that magic lamp.
你觉得怎么样
So what do you think?
我觉得那个妞可能挂了
I think that girl might be dead.
可我跟安迪怎么办
But what about me and Andy?
我们俩试过在一起很合拍 这不代表什么吗
I mean, you don't think it means something that we tested well.
我也经常试东试西 检测都呈阳性
Hey, I test positive for stuff all the time.
所以我不能捐血或输血
I'm not allowed to donate or get blood,
但除此之外 没啥问题啊
but other than that, it's cool.
我和安迪的确看起来很般配
Ugh, Andy and I do look great together.
万一美国比我还了解我自己呢
What if America knows more about me than I do?
那么我会觉得美国比我感觉中的更糟
Then I feel worse for America than I already do.
我不懂这有什么好值得商讨的
I-I don't know why any of this matters.
安迪知道你有男朋友了
Andy knows you have a boyfriend.
我没告诉他
I didn't tell him.
为什么我没告诉他
Why didn't I tell him?
沙马兰级的反转又来了
And boom goes the Shyamalan.
麦克斯 我问了他们没有巧克力牛奶
Hey, Max, they don't have chocolate milk, I asked.
那他们要我喝什么配虾啊
Ugh! How do they expect me to wash down my scrimps?
卡洛琳 我们能谈谈吗
Caroline, can we just talk
或许谈完后顺便共度下余生
and maybe spend the rest of our lives together?
放轻松就行
You know, keep it casual.
糖果先生
Hey! Mr. Candy guy!
把你的手从我女人身上拿开
Get your hands off my girl!
伙计 你把我喝的弄洒了
Dude, you spilled my drink!
她是我的女朋友
She's my girlfriend.
错了 她不是 你是谁来着
No, she is not. Who are you?
鲍比 你打翻醋缸打错人了
Bobby, you attacked the wrong Andy in a jealous rage.
真正的安迪在这里
He's over here.
你好呀 我该把我这杯喝的放下吗
Hey, how's it going? Should I put my drink down?
不用了 我已经够丢脸了
Ah, no...I've embarrassed myself enough.
对不起 卡洛琳 我只是无法忍受
I'm sorry, Caroline. I just couldn't stand
偷情早期你一周
the thought of you doing it with another guy
跟别的男人睡一次的想法
once a week in the beginning.
鲍比 我喜欢你吃醋
Bobby, I love that you're jealous--
吃醋到会使用暴力
violently jealous.
但你不需要这样
But you don't need to be.
安迪 我有男朋友了
Andy, I have a boyfriend.
一个吃醋到会使用暴力的男朋友
A violently jealous boyfriend.
我不觉得那算暴力
I wouldn't say violently.
我早上为了一块馅饼差点把你掐死
I choked you out for a Pop-Tart this morning.
好吧 现在真是超级尴尬
All right. Super awkward right now.
我猜我得去取消刚请来
Um, well, I guess I'm gonna have to go
为我们唱小夜曲的墨西哥街头乐队
cancel the Mariachi band I hired to serenade us.
再见 10块钱订金
Adios, $10 deposit.
你可以带他们来我们的甜品酒吧
Ooh, you should bring them by the dessert bar.
我邀请演员们来参加餐后聚会
I'm having an after party there with the cast.
是吗
We are?
这个嘛...现在你也受邀参加了
Mm, well...I guess now you're invited, too.
还有其他信息你可以用在戏里
And here's something else you can use.
通常我租车都租克莱斯勒
When I rent a car, I usually go with the Sebring.
我开始明白为什么我的戏份大部分被删掉了
I'm starting to see why they cut most of my scenes.
有一次我租了一辆丰田 就一次
Once I rented a Tercel. Once.
我得接个电话
I gotta take this.
我知道电话没响 但你懂的
I know it's not ringing, but you get it.
麻烦正牌阿憨站起来
Will the real Han please stand up?
然后离开
And then leave.
我去我的卡座了
I'll be in my booth.
我去我的卡错了
我去我的卡座了
I'll be in my booth.
我去我的卡错了
你就是领悟不到精髓
You just don't get it.
我能把酒跟五片红药片混在一起喝吗
Can I mix alcohol and, like, five red pills?
看我还站在这 你就知道可以啦
Ha, would I be standing here if you couldn't?
这可能看起来很怪 也或许是够重口
Uh, this might seem weird or maybe just freaky enough,
但我对那个妞饰演我的那部分很有性趣
but I am very attracted to that part of her that is me.
你知道吗 厄尔 如果你表现好
You know what, Earl? You play your cards right,
今晚你有可能睡"自己" 而不是自己睡
you might be screwing yourself tonight.
你好呀 妹子
What's up, girl?
我有告诉过你 我变得超级有钱吗
Did I tell you that I got super rich?
在六旗主题乐园受伤了
Yeah, got injured at Six Flags.
受伤的方式还挺窝囊
Not even in a cool way.
被一个胖娃绊倒 摔到一个瘦娃身上
Tripped on a fat kid, landed on a skinny kid.
或许你该去追求苔丝
Maybe you should go for Tess.
我敢说她很快就会变单身
I bet she'll be single soon
因为鲍比刚妒火爆发
since Bobby's jealous rage
把她男朋友烧得进医院了
sent her boyfriend to the hospital.
我才没有 我还要了他的签名
I did not. I got his autograph.
他在《疯狂动物城》里给一只小鹦鹉配音
He voiced a parakeet in Zootopia.
咕咕 想起来了吗
Cacaw. Ring a bell?
那我就在此别过了
Well, I guess this is good-bye.
下周的首映会我就不去了
I won't see you at the premiere next week.
我要去巴黎消愁解闷
I'm gonna go drown my sorrows in Paris.
还有巴厘岛
And Bali.
哪里有最贵的珠宝 我就去哪里
Well, wherever they have the most expensive jewels.
有话要对我说吗
Anything?
我就在这里
I'm right here.
你们千万不要因为我打架
Guys, don't fight over me
等我手机开始摄影后再打
until I have the camera open on my phone.
你真是一个幸运的家伙 鲍比
Well, you're a lucky guy, Bobby.
对了 她是一个非常可怕...
Just--by the way, she is a really horrible...
算了 我想不出来缺点
No, I can't think of anything.
她非常完美
She's pretty perfect.
我相信如果你用心去寻找
I'm sure if you tried really hard
你会找到那个人 她会愿意跟
you'll find someone willing to date
一个正值美好年华的魅力多金男人约会
a very attractive rich guy in the prime of his life.
你说得我都想跟他约会了
Now you're making me want to date him.
好了 我该走了
Well, I better get going.
一到晚八点 直升飞机就堵得飞不动了
Helicopter traffic gets crazy at 8:00.
有话要对我说吗
Anything?
直升飞机
Helicopter?
我一直在试图找瓦妮莎
I've been trying to look for Vanessa,
但她现在可能换成她的帮派名字了
but she probably goes by her gang name, now.
我在我的警方通讯接收器找不到她
I couldn't find her on my police scanner,
但这玩意帮我躲过把大麻买给卧底警察
but it did help me avoid selling weed to an undercover cop.
收到 长官
Copy that, Sarge.
好了 奥列格 走吧
All right, Oleg. Let's go.
今天周三 我们得把垃圾拿出来
It's Wednesday, so we gotta take the garbage out
好让我们能在水槽下啪啪啪
so we can do it under the sink.
水管工式性交
Ooh, plumber style.
苏菲
Sophie.
那不是我
That's not me.
可是老天 他太棒了
But my God, he is gorgeous.
我曾有一次做过这种春梦
I had a dream like this once.
只是当时我满身涂满牛轧糖
Only I was covered in nougat.
走吧 两个随便一个
Let's go, one of the Olegs.
走啦 麦克斯
All right, bye, Max.
你好 麦克斯
Oh, hi, Max.
麦克斯 瓦妮莎来了
Max? Vanessa's here!
天啊 你会没事的
Oh, my God. You're gonna be okay.
继续喝 你只是因为想太快成为我
Just keep drinking. You tried being me too fast.
-我... -别说话 喝吧
- I just-- - Don't talk, drink.
你怎么这样还能没死啊
How are you not dead?
你看见了吗
Did you see that?
她从来没这样轻拍过我的头
She's never patted my head like that.
她有次还给我兑换一次拍头的生日礼券
And she even gave me a birthday coupon for one free head pat.
我是闻到一股醋味了吗
Is that jealousy I see?
我和麦克斯情比金坚
Max and I are in a strong relationship.
我才没有吃醋
I am not jealous.
她们俩是紧紧地拥抱在一起了吗
Are they in a full-on hug now?
我要去兑换我的礼券了
I'm redeeming my coupon.
有话要对我说吗
Anything?
没有吗 那停吧
No? Okay, cut it.
好吧 走吧 谁想坐直升飞机
Uh, all right, come on. Who likes helicopter rides?
直升飞机
Helicopter?